ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Files /4283
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Program Files. H&S - Program no. 2161- 2394. (Box 202)
  - HazCom, 2001 (Box 202, Folder 50)
    WNYCOSH, #2389
  - Conf. Sp. (Box 202, Folder 51)
    WNYCOSH, #2390
  - MCWA- HazCom and PPE, 2001 (Box 202, Folder 52)
    ROCOSH, #2391, 10/31/01
  - Crisis Prevention and Management- Buffalo, 2001 (Box 202, Folder 53)
    #2392, 12/3/01
  - Stress- Buffalo, 2001 (Box 202, Folder 54)
    #2393, 12/4/01
  - Crisis- Rochester, 2002 (Box 202, Folder 55)
    #2394, 4/15/02
- SHRM Manuals and correspondence. (Box 203)
  - SHRM Learning System- Online Information, 2002 (Box 203, Folder 1)
  - Building a Course Website, 2001 (Box 203, Folder 2)
  - SHRM Online Course, 2000 (Box 203, Folder 3)
  - ECASB Directory, Human Resource Management, 2002 (Box 203, Folder 4)
  - SHRM Learning System Instructor's Materials, 2002 (Box 203, Folder 5)
  - SHRM Learning System Part 1, 2001 (Box 203, Folder 6)
  - SHRM Learning System Part 2, 2001 (Box 203, Folder 7)
  - SHRM Learning System Part 3, 2001 (Box 203, Folder 8)
  - Office of Labor Management Standards, 1987-1989 (Box 203, Folder 9)
  - Labor Organization Annual Report, 1987 (Box 203, Folder 10)
  - Labor Organization Annual Report, 1987 (Box 203, Folder 11)
  - SHRM Learning System, 1999-2004 (Box 203, Folder 12)
    CD's Labelled "SHRM Power Point Slides"
- #5 West Hall Program Files. 2003-2004. (Box 204)
  - Collective Bargaining Coaching, 2003 (Box 204, Folder 1)
    03W064, 10/8/03, Henderson
  - Strategic Planning and Dynamics of Labor Negotiations, 2003 (Box 204, Folder 2)
    03W061-62
  - Health Care Ind. Assoc, Domestic Violence, Project Management, Strategic Contract Campaigns, UAW-Special Program, Leadership, 2003 (Box 204, Folder 3)
    03W056-60
  - Focus Group Eval Session, 2003 (Box 204, Folder 4)
    Mentholatum, 03W052, 8/14/03, Henderson
  - Domestic Violence: A Workplace Issue, 2003 (Box 204, Folder 5)
  - Strategic Contract Campaigns, 2003 (Box 204, Folder 6)
    10/17/03
  - High Road Economics at Work, 2004 (Box 204, Folder 7)
    03W051, 2/27/04
  - Registrations, 2004 (Box 204, Folder 8)
  - Brochure Mailing, 2004 (Box 204, Folder 9)
    2/27/04
  - High Road Economics at Work, Low Wage America, 2004 (Box 204, Folder 10)
    Contains 5 booklets and some papers
  - Current Trends in Mfg. and EEO Laws and Responsibilities, 2003 (Box 204, Folder 11)
    03W066-67
  - Unions and Collective Bargaining, 2004 (Box 204, Folder 12)
- Program manuals. (Box 205)
  - First Regular PEL Part 1, 1989 (Box 205, Folder 1)
  - First Regular PEL Part 2, 1989 (Box 205, Folder 2)
  - First Regular PEL Part 3, 1989 (Box 205, Folder 3)
  - 2001: A Vision in Progress (Revised), 1997 (Box 205, Folder 4)
  - 2001: A Vision in Progress, 1997 (Box 205, Folder 5)
  - 2001: A Vision in Progress (Proposal Draft), 1997 (Box 205, Folder 6)
  - A Guide to Information on Closely Held Corporations, 1986 (Box 205, Folder 7)
  - A Labor Relations Primer, 2000 (Box 205, Folder 8)
  - A Labor Relations Primer- DJC Part 1, 2000 (Box 205, Folder 9)
  - A Labor Relations Primer- DJC Part 2, 2000 (Box 205, Folder 10)
  - A Labor Relations Primer- Facilitator Part 1, 2000 (Box 205, Folder 11)
  - A Labor Relations Primer- Facilitator Part 2, 2000 (Box 205, Folder 12)
  - A Mediation Model for Workplace Disputes Part 1, 1997 (Box 205, Folder 13)
  - A Mediation Model for Workplace Disputes Part 2, 1997 (Box 205, Folder 14)
  - ADA Update 2002 Part 1 (Box 205, Folder 15)
  - ADA Update 2002 Part 2 (Box 205, Folder 16)
  - Administering Progressive Discipline, 1997 (Box 205, Folder 17)
  - Administering Progressive Discipline and Avoiding Wrongful Discharge, 1998 (Box 205, Folder 18)
  - Advanced Training Program Part 1, 1991 (Box 205, Folder 19)
  - Advanced Training Program Part 2, 1991 (Box 205, Folder 20)
  - Advanced Training Program, 1992 (Box 205, Folder 21)
  - AFL CIO Leadership Training Manual, 1989 (Box 205, Folder 22)
  - After the Training, 1993 (Box 205, Folder 23)
  - AIS Introduction Material, 2003 (Box 205, Folder 24)
  - AIS Introduction Material, 2004 (Box 205, Folder 25)
- Program manuals. (Box 206)
  - AIS Introduction Material Part 1, 2005 (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - AIS Introduction Material Part 2, 2005 (Box 206, Folder 2)
  - AIS Introduction Material Part 1, 2006 (Box 206, Folder 3)
  - AIS Introduction Material Part 2, 2006 (Box 206, Folder 4)
  - Alternate Dispute Resolution, 1997 (Box 206, Folder 5)
  - Alternate Dispute Resolution in the Workplace, 1997 (Box 206, Folder 6)
  - Americans with Disabilities Act Handbook Part 1, 1991 (Box 206, Folder 7)
  - Americans with Disabilities Act Handbook Part 2, 1991 (Box 206, Folder 8)
  - ADA: Impact, 1992 (Box 206, Folder 9)
  - An Interest Based Approach, 2000 (Box 206, Folder 10)
  - An Interest Based Approach to Problem Solving, 2002 (Box 206, Folder 11)
  - Arbitration (Box 206, Folder 12)
  - Arbitration Techniques Part 1 (Box 206, Folder 13)
  - Arbitration Techniques Part 2 (Box 206, Folder 14)
  - Arbitration Training for USWA Local 593, 1998 (Box 206, Folder 15)
  - Attitudes of Labor Union, 1990 (Box 206, Folder 16)
  - Auto Industry in Transition (Box 206, Folder 17)
  - Banking on People, 2005 (Box 206, Folder 18)
  - Basic Supervisory Skills Training, 1988 (Box 206, Folder 19)
  - Better Business Writing, 2001 (Box 206, Folder 20)
  - Biz Wiz, 2001 (Box 206, Folder 21)
  - Building a Collaborative Work Environment (Box 206, Folder 22)
  - Building Better Workplace Relationships, 1998 (Box 206, Folder 23)
- Program manuals. (Box 207)
  - Building Labor Management Relations, 2000 (Box 207, Folder 1)
    February
  - Building Labor Management Relations, 2000 (Box 207, Folder 2)
    June
  - Business Math, 2000 (Box 207, Folder 3)
  - Chautaugua County Labor Management, 2000 (Box 207, Folder 4)
  - Collective Bargaining and Labor Relations, 1987 (Box 207, Folder 5)
  - Collective Bargaining and Labor Relations, 1992 (Box 207, Folder 6)
  - Collective Bargaining for Mutual Gains Part 1, 1998 (Box 207, Folder 7)
  - Collective Bargaining for Mutual Gains Part 2, 1998 (Box 207, Folder 8)
  - Commissioners Management and Leadership Seminar, 1991 (Box 207, Folder 9)
  - Common Sense Economics Part 1, 1997 (Box 207, Folder 10)
  - Common Sense Economics Part 2, 1997 (Box 207, Folder 11)
  - Common Sense Economics Part 1, 1997 (Box 207, Folder 12)
  - Common Sense Economics Part 2, 1997 (Box 207, Folder 13)
  - Communication Skills Seminar, 1988 (Box 207, Folder 14)
  - Conference on the detection, Prevention of the Problem Drinking, 1975 (Box 207, Folder 15)
  - Connections: Succeeding in an Interrelated World, 2000 (Box 207, Folder 16)
  - Contract Bargaining, 1997 (Box 207, Folder 17)
  - Contract Interpretation and Implementation, 1991 (Box 207, Folder 18)
  - Contract Interpretation and Implementation, 2001 (Box 207, Folder 19)
  - Contract Interpretation and Implementation, 2001 (Box 207, Folder 20)
  - Contract Interpretation and Implementation, 2001 (Box 207, Folder 21)
  - Copper and Brass Industry Presentation Notes, 1994 (Box 207, Folder 22)
  - Copper and Brass Industry Overheads (Box 207, Folder 23)
    Contains Overhead Slides
  - Court Referred ADR in NY State, 1995 (Box 207, Folder 24)
  - Court Referred ADR in NY State, 1996 (Box 207, Folder 25)
  - Creating and Managing a Corporate University Partnership, 1998 (Box 207, Folder 26)
  - Creating and Sustaining Effective Organizations, 1992 (Box 207, Folder 27)
- Program manuals. (Box 208)
  - Creative Problem Solving Building a Relationship, 2001 (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - Cultural Diversity: Training Materials, 1994 (Box 208, Folder 2)
  - CWA/Bellsouth Facing the Challenge, 1992 (Box 208, Folder 3)
  - Data Analysis for EEO (Box 208, Folder 4)
  - Delphi 5 Vol. 1&2, 2000 (Box 208, Folder 5)
  - Delphi 6 Vol. 1-3, 2000 (Box 208, Folder 6)
  - Directory of Certified Minority and Women Part 1, 1986 (Box 208, Folder 7)
  - Directory of Certified Minority and Women Part 2, 1986 (Box 208, Folder 8)
  - Directory of Labor Unions and Employee Org., 1992 (Box 208, Folder 9)
  - Discipline and Grievance Procedures, 2001 (Box 208, Folder 10)
  - Dollars and Sense (Box 208, Folder 11)
  - Dynamics of Handling Employee Complaints, 1998 (Box 208, Folder 12)
  - E2 Education Phase II Participant Manual, 2000 (Box 208, Folder 13)
  - E2 Instructors Manual (Box 208, Folder 14)
  - E2 Participants Manual (Box 208, Folder 15)
  - Economics of Employee Benefits w/Enroll, 1994 (Box 208, Folder 16)
  - Economic Strategies for Collective Bargaining (Box 208, Folder 17)
  - Economic Strategies for Collective Bargaining, 1997 (Box 208, Folder 18)
  - Economic Strategies for Collective Bargaining, 1997 (Box 208, Folder 19)
  - Education for Empowerment (Box 208, Folder 20)
  - Education for Empowerment Instructor (Box 208, Folder 21)
  - EEO 2000 Data Analysis, 1997 (Box 208, Folder 22)
  - EEO Selection and Performance, 1997 (Box 208, Folder 23)
  - EEO 2000 ADA, 1997 (Box 208, Folder 24)
- Program manuals. (Box 209)
  - EEO Family and Medical Leave, 1996 (Box 209, Folder 1)
  - EEO 2000: Preventing Sexual Harassment, 1996 (Box 209, Folder 2)
  - EEO Mediation Training Part 1, 1992 (Box 209, Folder 3)
  - EEO Mediation Training Part 2, 1992 (Box 209, Folder 4)
  - EEO Selection and Performance Management Part 1 (Box 209, Folder 5)
  - EEO Selection and Performance Management Part 2 (Box 209, Folder 6)
  - EEOC/Cornell Mediation Training, 1998 (Box 209, Folder 7)
  - EEOC/Cornell Mediation Training (Box 209, Folder 8)
  - Effective Interviewing, 1998 (Box 209, Folder 9)
  - Effective Management Manual 5th Edition Part 1, 1992 (Box 209, Folder 10)
  - Effective Management Manual 5th Edition Part 2, 1992 (Box 209, Folder 11)
  - Effective Management Manual 5th Edition Part 3, 1992 (Box 209, Folder 12)
  - Effective Management Manual 5th Edition Part 1, 1995 (Box 209, Folder 13)
  - Effective Management Manual 5th Edition Part 2, 1995 (Box 209, Folder 14)
  - Effective Use of Arbitration (Box 209, Folder 15)
  - Effective Ways of Dealing with Employee Behavior (Box 209, Folder 16)
  - Effective Ways of Dealing With Employee Behavior (Box 209, Folder 17)
  - Employee Relations, 1997 (Box 209, Folder 18)
  - Employment in Europe, 1998 (Box 209, Folder 19)
  - Employment in Europe, 1998 (Box 209, Folder 20)
  - Facilitation Skills Resource Volume 1, 2000 (Box 209, Folder 21)
  - Facilitation Skills Resource Manual Volume 2, 2000 (Box 209, Folder 22)
  - Facilitation Skills Training, 1993 (Box 209, Folder 23)
- E-Institute for Leadership 2001 -- pulled from box 20, folder 22 (Box 210)
  - E-Institute for Leadership 2001 -- May 17, 2001 -- pulled from box 20, folder 22 (Box 210, Folder 1)
    Alliance of New York State Arts Organizations Distant Modules (6)
  - PEL, 1998 (Box 210, Folder 2)